<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Kacy's blog</title><link>/</link><description>Recent content on Kacy's blog</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 19:00:00 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Welcome to my Blog</title><link>/post/welcome/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 20:12:11 -0400</pubDate><guid>/post/welcome/</guid><description>Hello everyone,
Welcome to my blog!
Why GitHub Pages? Github page is offering free online static page. Starting a static page in github maybe is a easier way for individuals who prefer not to rely on existing online blog platforms.
Unlike holding a website server on AWS which can be costly and vulnerable to random attacks from online sources, GitHub Pages provides a user-friendly solution for those who simply want to manage a blog without the complexities of traditional web hosting.</description></item><item><title>Create Personal Page</title><link>/post/create-personal-page/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 19:00:00 -0400</pubDate><guid>/post/create-personal-page/</guid><description>Why Create Personal Page In the past, I used to maintain a server on AWS, essentially transforming it into my own personalized cloud drive and a platform for writing blogs. However, this setup incurred expenses and proved to be quite challenging to utilize effectively as a blog publishing platform. It felt akin to having a computer online, complete with virtual machines and various tools like lambda. Over time, as AWS</description></item><item><title>About Me</title><link>/about.html</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 00:07:06 -0400</pubDate><guid>/about.html</guid><description>This blog is to record the learning notes ~
Is Me Highly skilled and motivated Embedded Firmware and Software Engineer in the full software development life cycle for IoT and real-time control applications. Proficient in C/C++, Python, Jira, Git, SVN and microcontroller development with a proven track record of delivering software functionalities on time, within budget, and maintaining high quality standards. Adept at debugging, troubleshooting, problem-solving, and technical documentation while working efficiently under pressure in fast-paced environments.</description></item><item><title>Others</title><link>/others.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2023 15:04:05 -0700</pubDate><guid>/others.html</guid><description>Here is the List of the blog
Welcome Blog</description></item></channel></rss>