<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><search><entry><title>Create Personal Page</title><url>/blog/create-personal-page/</url><categories><category><no value=/></categories><tags><tag><no value=/><tag><no value=/></tags><content type="html"> Create Personal Page Hugo There are many syntax and theme. After using the orignal blank version and the minima, hugo seems to be more organize for user who has different topic in one blog (Yes, is me. Putting all the note).
Hugo provide a method to maintain the article organized and sepeate the maintain file and the public file. Also, there are theme in thire website who is free to download. Thank you all of the contributors providing beautiful structure ~~
One more key point is, Hugo provide offline preview with local server. Which means user can preview the blog before upload to github and make it public. Another words, it can be used as a private notes server instand of creating a database server. I created one for saving my gaming walkthroughs in local as a test. it is very useful for someone like me don&amp;rsquo;t want to create a local database server with file system or who want to create their own personal website.</content></entry><entry><title>Welcome to my Blog</title><url>/welcome/</url><categories/><tags/><content type="html"> Hello everyone,
Welcome to my blog!
Why GitHub Pages? Github page is offering free online static page. Starting a static page in github maybe is a easier way for individuals who prefer not to rely on existing online blog platforms.
Unlike holding a website server on AWS which can be costly and vulnerable to random attacks from online sources, GitHub Pages provides a user-friendly solution for those who simply want to manage a blog without the complexities of traditional web hosting.
Furture plan The website is updating as this is not the final syntax or style I want and I am continuously working on it. As a software engineer with coding knowledge, I intend to make various changes that align with my vision and preferences.
In addition to refining the website, I am excited to share my journey of continuous learning with all of you. Through blog posts, I will document not only the technical aspects of web development but also other areas of my learning process.
Whether it&amp;rsquo;s exploring new programming languages, diving into the world of data science, or uncovering the latest trends in artificial intelligence, I aim to provide valuable insights and resources. By sharing these experiences, I hope to inspire others to embark on their own learning adventures and foster a community of knowledge-sharing.
Stay Hungry Stay Foolish
Let&amp;rsquo;s embrace our curiosity and never stop seeking new knowledge.
Thank you for joining me on this exciting blogging journey. I look forward to sharing valuable content and connecting with you all!</content></entry><entry><title>About Me</title><url>/about.html</url><categories/><tags/><content type="html"> About Me
Is Me Just want to record the learning process</content></entry><entry><title>BLOG LIST</title><url>/bloglist.html</url><categories/><tags/><content type="html"> Here is the List of the blog
Welcome Blog</content></entry></search>