<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on Kacy's blog</title><link>/post/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on Kacy's blog</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 18:30:00 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/post/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Welcome to my Blog</title><link>/post/welcome/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 20:12:11 -0400</pubDate><guid>/post/welcome/</guid><description>Hello everyone,
Welcome to my blog!
Why GitHub Pages? Github page is offering free online static page. Starting a static page in github maybe is a easier way for individuals who prefer not to rely on existing online blog platforms.
Unlike holding a website server on AWS which can be costly and vulnerable to random attacks from online sources, GitHub Pages provides a user-friendly solution for those who simply want to manage a blog without the complexities of traditional web hosting.</description></item><item><title>Create Personal Page</title><link>/post/create-personal-page/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 18:30:00 -0400</pubDate><guid>/post/create-personal-page/</guid><description>Why Create Personal Page In the past, I used to maintain a server on AWS, essentially transforming it into my own personalized cloud drive and a platform for writing blogs. However, this setup incurred expenses and proved to be quite challenging to utilize effectively as a blog publishing platform. It felt akin to having a computer online, complete with virtual machines and various tools like lambda. Over time, as AWS</description></item><item><title>Create Own Theme</title><link>/post/create-own-theme/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2023 20:00:00 -0400</pubDate><guid>/post/create-own-theme/</guid><description>Create New Theme If you cannot find the theme that you like, you can create your own Hugo theme. Creating a custom Hugo theme allows you to have complete control over the design and functionality of your website. Here&amp;rsquo;s a step-by-step guide on how to create your own Hugo theme: Create a new theme directory Start by creating a new directory for your theme. You can name it whatever you</description></item></channel></rss>